Gaby, Alex Papers 5889
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Alex Gaby Papers
1941-1989
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Gaby, Alex
5889
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
5725213
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 01, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Mr. Gaby served for 31 years as editor of the Labor News, the weekly voice of the AFL-CIO in Rochester, In 1979, he became the assistant industrial commissioner in charge of the state Department of Labor's Rochester office. Mr. Gaby was also a fiction writer and had short stories published in The Saturday Evening Post, Collier's and The New Yorker.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6239: Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Records
Gaby, Alex
5725213
- Biographical, 1941-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Awards, 1979-1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Retirement, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Essays and Short Stories (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Literary Correspondence, 1941-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Writing, 1942-1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Scrapbook, 1947-1950 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Labor News Editing, 1961-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Assistant Industrial Commissioner for the State of New York, 1979-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- NYS Department of Labor Weekly Reports, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- NYS Department of Labor Weekly Report, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- NYS Department of Labor Weekly Report, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Israel, 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Drug Decriminalization, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Carpenter's Union (Box 1, Folder 15)
- High School Curriculum, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- US Army, 1942-1962 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Michael Dukakis, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Stephen Hammer (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Sam Cenname (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Other Rochester, NY Writers (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 22)